=Let's Go Fighting= =Episode 27=
= لنبدأ القتال = = الحلقة 27 =
You'll explain later.
سوف تشرح لاحقا.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
It's your script!
إنه البرنامج النصي الخاص بك!
You're all here.
أنتم جميعا هنا.
Don't you have aphasia,
ألا تعاني من الحبسة الكلامية ،
amnesia,
فقدان الذاكرة،
and mobility problems?
ومشاكل التنقل؟
Don't you have a neural meningioma?
أليس لديك ورم سحائي عصبي؟
I even showed the report
حتى أنني عرضت التقرير
to foreign experts.
للخبراء الأجانب.
Couldn't you be more careful
لا يمكن أن تكون أكثر حذرا
when you were faking it?
عندما كنت تزييفها؟
I can explain.
أستطيع أن أشرح.
Li,
لي ،
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
Li,
لي ،
I...
أنا...
Do you know why I believed
هل تعلم لماذا آمنت
your nonsense?
هراءك؟
Do you know what terminal illness
هل تعرف ما هو مرض عضال
means to me?
يعني لي؟
Since childhood,
منذ الطفولة،
I've been kept alive
لقد ظللت على قيد الحياة
by medical equipment.
بالمعدات الطبية.
My parents are gone
رحل والداي
and so is my sister.
وكذلك أختي.
Do you know
هل تعرف
what you mean to me?
ماذا تعني لي؟
what I should do
ما يجب أن أقوم به
if something happens to you?
إذا حدث لك شيء؟
♪Some of the past is hard to forget♪
♪ من الصعب نسيان بعض الماضي
♪Some people stay in memory♪
♪ بعض الناس يظلون في الذاكرة
Mu Li.
مو لي.
Don't go!
لا تذهب!
Mu Li,
مو لي ،
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I know
أنا أعرف
I let you down.
خذلتك.
I don't know how to express it.
لا أعرف كيف أعبر عنها.
It's my childishness
إنها طفولتي
that broke your heart.
حطم قلبك.
But I never wanted
لكنني لم أرغب أبدًا
to lie to you.
لتكذب عليك.
I didn't want
لا اريد
to use you.
لاستخدامك.
I just don't want to lose you.
أنا فقط لا أريد أن أفقدك.
That's I used
هذا اعتدت عليه
this stupid method.
هذه الطريقة الغبية.
I thought
اعتقدت
I could keep you.
يمكنني الاحتفاظ بك.
Mu Li,
مو لي ،
I...
أنا...
I love you.
أحبك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
♪I can't participate in your future♪
♪ لا أستطيع المشاركة في مستقبلك ♪
♪A long distance is left♪
بقيت مسافة طويلة ♪
♪Love is complex♪
الحب معقد ♪
♪Someone gave up♪
♪ شخص ما استسلم
♪Someone's still going on♪
♪ شخص ما مازال مستمرا ♪
♪The real love gotten by fighting♪
الحب الحقيقي الذي حصل عليه القتال ♪
♪Is discarded in the end♪
♪ يتم التخلص منها في النهاية ♪
I'm wondering
انا اتسائل
what Miss Mu will choose.
ماذا ستختار الآنسة مو.
Ha ha.
هاها.
Come in.
ادخل.
Boss,
رئيس،
here are
هنا
all the reports
كل التقارير
about Starwu's investment business.
حول الأعمال الاستثمارية Starwu.
Some have been sued
تمت مقاضاة البعض
by the Mu Group.
بواسطة مجموعة Mu.
The rest has low valuations.
الباقي تقييمات منخفضة.
Then do something to make them higher.
ثم افعل شيئًا لجعلها أعلى.
I'm wondering
انا اتسائل
what the hell you did when you worked
ماذا فعلت بحق الجحيم عندما عملت
for my stupid brother.
لأخي الغبي.
Li,
لي ،
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
It's my bad idea.
إنها فكرتي السيئة.
I don't blame you.
أنا لا ألومك.
Mo Chen and I
مو تشن وأنا
have to thank you both.
يجب أن أشكركم على حد سواء.
Huh?
هاه؟
So you've made up?
إذن لقد اختلقت؟
Yes.
نعم.
Great!
رائعة!
Jack shall have Jill.
جاك يجب أن يكون عنده جيل.
How did you make up?
كيف صنعت؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Mo Feng has laid hands on the industrial park.
وضع مو فنغ يده على المنطقة الصناعية.
Now they are in the meeting room.
هم الآن في غرفة الاجتماعات.
(Mu Group)
(مجموعة مو)
Miss Mu,
ملكة جمال مو ،
you finally came.
جئت أخيرا.
Mo Feng,
مو فنغ ،
what do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
The project of the Fashion Food Industrial Park
مشروع فاشون فود اندستريال بارك
is a key project
هو مشروع رئيسي
of the Mu Group now, isn't it?
من مجموعة Mu الآن ، أليس كذلك؟
What do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
The person in charge of the park
الشخص المسؤول عن الحديقة
came and talked to me,
جاء وتحدث معي ،
hoping to get more investment.
أملا في الحصول على مزيد من الاستثمار.
Don't try to inject the funds of MOHS.
لا تحاول ضخ أموال وزارة الصحة والخدمات الاجتماعية.
Then,
ثم،
the industrial project
المشروع الصناعي
that we have won
التي فزنا بها
will be lost.
ستكون ضائعا.
Even if we lose the industrial park,
حتى لو فقدنا المنطقة الصناعية ،
I won't support the introduction of new funds,
لن أؤيد إدخال أموال جديدة ،
which will dilute
مما سيخفف
everyone's equity.
حقوق الجميع.
Since everyone has no intention,
بما أن الجميع ليس لديه نية ،
this meeting is unnecessary.
هذا الاجتماع غير ضروري.
It doesn't matter to me.
لا يهمني.
If the industrial park project is lost,
إذا ضاع مشروع المجمع الصناعي ،
my poor brother
أخي المسكين
will be kicked out again.
سيتم طرده مرة أخرى.
You should think it over.
يجب أن تفكر في الأمر.
Hem.
هدب.
Oops.
أُووبس.
=Let's Go Fighting=
= لنبدأ القتال =
♪The soul falls to the bottom of the lake♪
الروح تسقط في قاع البحيرة
♪Broken stars pierce the sky♪
♪ النجوم المكسورة تخترق السماء ♪
♪Secrets hidden in the cloud♪
♪ أسرار مخبأة في السحابة ♪
♪From the Milky Way♪
♪ من درب التبانة ♪
♪Belong to you♪
ملك لك ♪